Hello everyone. Welcome back to today's another new tutorial topic. So, to this topic here updating the MongoDB documents using the MongoDB shares, okay.
So, now just let's start and perfectly explore how to update the comments in the MongoDB collections using the various update operations and so on.
And now first of all, I can collect for here the students. So, then I can just use for
students collection. So, now just we are already in another table. So, inside we can see the
so now that we can open this shell, okay. So, you can see now first of all, I can go in for so first of all
here, I'm going for students, okay. So, it's T, E, D, N, T, S students, okay. And now just use the review and the students.
And now we can perfectly use a new session perfectly collecting this MongoDB. And
from going for first step, we can updating the this shell, okay. And now I can just go here
first of all type the DB dot and use for the collections name, suppose example.
So, STU, D, N, T students, the first of all here I can type this is the update for
suppose like this update one, okay. Now I can create the parentheses and create the curly bracket
sign and everything so I can define for the name. So, the name is double quotation, the fine
button, suppose right here the name is John, okay. Now here I create for I can type another. So,
I can create the curly bracket. So, in this instance, I can use for the last sign and the function
and again use the curly bracket and here it's defined for the this one, okay. So, now here
simply defined for this tab, age and name. So, now commonly, there's a single document in the
collection where the name feels this one to say the age is certified, okay. So, update one,
just here and I can just now here I can choose for the same name. So, I can use the
Johan and it's defined for certified. So, check here then first and last name that address and I can
see the perfectly this acknowledgement is true and inside here the match for perfectly
move on, okay. So, here this is perfectly open this statement and now here the MongoDB
success pool update the document, okay. So, next step here I can go in for another example and
I can just define now updating for the multiple documents, okay. So, now just going here and first of
all we can update the multiple documents. So, now first of all I'm type for the DB dot give the
students, okay dot dot. So, I have this update many function, okay. So, this on update too many
and now in this inside here first define the curly bracket, okay. So, now I can define it for the
settings. So, settings is defined perfectly just new here, okay. Then the perfectly strategy
the new here and now for the space disown the perfect. So, now here you can use the again the
curly bracket and here I can use for the dollar sign and type for the same function, okay.
Now here is for the 18 and then parenthesis and type for here the newly added status,
so defined for this status is defined. So, now I can go clear this status is active, okay.
So, here this perfectly defined for the active status and disown perfectly created for this
command for document and in the students information over the created the new one and completely
different interface. So, now place the entire and you can see manually acknowledgement perfectly
update the multiple columns, okay. So, you can see here perfectly this statement is working
and in this session here perfectly use for the two statements the first update one and update
nine and you can see here it is perfectly working this so now just we are ready. It is the database section
and I hope you perfectly understand this session is completely done and we are happy for updating
the MongoDB documents using for the information or the MongoDB shell, okay. I hope you find
this tutorial helpful and you have perfectly understand the MongoDB update collection, okay.
So, thank you for watching and happy coding.